<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Uninformed Priors</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Uninformed Priors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Commercial Bank Feasibility with R</title>
      <link>/posts/analyzing-commercial-bank-feasibility-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</author>
      <guid>/posts/analyzing-commercial-bank-feasibility-with-r/</guid>
      <description>Intro Lately I have been doing some consulting work on the topic of commercial bank feasibility in the state of Idaho. My client is interested in looking at potential under-serviced markets they could expand to. While I won’t publish specific data concerning my client, I thought this could be a good opportunity to play with some public data published by the Bureau of Labor Statistics, US Census Bureau, FDIC and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy Tuesday Week 02</title>
      <link>/posts/tidy-tuesday-week-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</author>
      <guid>/posts/tidy-tuesday-week-02/</guid>
      <description>This post will walk us through the second week of #TidyTuesday. #TidyTuesday is a weekly social data project put on by the R for Data Science learning community. Every week a data set, article, and graphic are posted and users are encouraged to either recreate the graphic themselves using R or create their own take on the graphic using the data provided.
This week, we’ll be using data from a fivethirtyeight article, “Running Backs are Finnaly Getting Paid what they are Worth”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using purrr to wrangle and clean economic data</title>
      <link>/posts/using-purrr-to-wrangle-and-clean-economic-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</author>
      <guid>/posts/using-purrr-to-wrangle-and-clean-economic-data/</guid>
      <description>I’m currently working on building a quantitative macroeconomics course with a professor of mine. The goal of the course is to introduce students within the Economics department to programming in Python and R. This is a big step for our department. Even though we have always been a fairly math heavy econ degree, the department has been stuck behind the curve in teaching students new and up-to-date technical skills. This professor, along with my help, wants to move the courses away from teaching STATA and Excel, to equipping students with proper data analysis tools for the workforce and academia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy Tuesday Week 01</title>
      <link>/posts/tidy-tuesday-week-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dylan.mcdowell226@gmail.com (Dylan McDowell)</author>
      <guid>/posts/tidy-tuesday-week-01/</guid>
      <description>Here are some R libraries we will need to reproduce the plots for this week’s #TidyTuesday
library(tidyverse) library(readxl) library(albersusa) library(ggthemes)  Background The online community, R for Data Science, has started what’s called #TidyTuesday. Every week they post a new dataset along with an original graphic and challenge people to either 1) recreate the plot or 2) create their own take on the data. For the very first challenge, they posted a data set on student tuition across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>